<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">There is no help available at this time.</string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">Help is available for each section of this app.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">Application for personal time statistic.</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">General</string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
<![CDATA[
      <p>Main screen application have 4 tabs: counters, records, diagrams and diary.</p>
      <p><img src="hlp_main_act">
      </p>
      <p>
      On the counter, you can create, edit and delete counters.<b> Counter is the action </b>.
      When you create or edit, you can to specify the name and color of the tile counter.
      Deleting counter leads to the removal of all records relating to him, be careful.      By default, works <b> Idle </ b> the counter, it will switch to it, if you click on the working counter.
      That is, it is used for excluding downtime, &#34;unnecessary&#34; time and so on.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">Edit records</string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
<![CDATA[
		<h1>General</h1>
      <p> The app leads "pass-through statistic", i.e., accounting of all your time.
It can not be stopped as it is impossible to stop time, so it is sometimes necessary to edit the record.</p>
		<p> I came up with two ways to edit of records, the first - a partition of records, the second - the combination of records.
		You can send me your ideas about how to edit records, always happy to discuss!</p>
		<h1>A partition of records </h1>
		<p> A partition occurs on the &#34;Records&#34;, just click on the edited record and dialogue will open. </p>
		<p><img src="hlp_cutting_rec"></p>
		<p> The dialogue is possible to change the name to record and edit the start time (tstart) and end time (tstop).
		Start record can only move forward (t1 more tstart), then before the edited record will be one more, with a start time, as in the original recording (tstart) and end time, equal to the new start time (t1).
		In addition, the end of the recording, you can only move back (t2 is less than tstop), then after the edited record will be one more, with a start time equal to this new value (t2) and end time equal to the original (tstop). For example:
		</p>
        <p><img src="hlp_edit_rec"></p>
      <h1>Combination of records.</h1>
      <p> In order to combine records, you must activate the combining using the a long press on the first record:</p>
      <p><img src="hlp_union_rec"></p>
      <p> After that, the records appear right checkboxes allow you to select consecutive records to combine. 
      Upon completion of selection and clicking on &#34;Combine&#34; to open a dialog where you can specify a name for the new record, the defaul it will fit most of the selected records:</p>
      <p><img src="hlp_union_dlg"></p>
      <h1>Delete counters</h1>
      <p> In addition to editing of records, you can delete the counter, which is not used or is not needed.
      But please note that it will be impossible to restore back the recording.</p>
      <h1>Edite data base</h1>
      <p> Besides the possibilities of this program, records can be edited directly in the database.
      It has sqlite format and simple structure. Structure is described in the relevant section.</p>
       ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">Structure of database</string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
<![CDATA[
	  <h1>General</h1>
      <p> 
The application works with a database <b>timestat.db</b>. Usually it is located in the phone&#39;s memory:
      </p>
      <p>Path:/data/data/maximsblog.blogspot.com.timestatistic/databases
      </p>
      <p> If your phone has a root-access, you can edit the database on this (or similar) way. 
      Otherwise, you can export the database, then edit it and import it back.
      Personally, I use this program SQLite Editor.</p>
      <h1>Tables and fields</h1>
      <p> While the application is using two tables:</p>
      <p>timers</p>
      <p>times</p>
      <p>notes</p>
      <h2>timers</h2>
      <p> The table &#34;timers&#34; are attributes counters. Description of column is: id - the identifier of the counter; name - his name; color - color; isrunning - 1, if run and 0 if stop (<b> Attention! </ b> can be started only one counter, that can only be one unit, otherwise the program will fall); interval - Time in milliseconds between reminders</p>
      <h2>times</h2>
      <p> This table stores the records themselves. Description of columns: _idt - record identifier; timerid - counter identifier (it matches the value of the _id table timers); start - the start time, in milliseconds, class java DateTime; length - the length of records in milliseconds; endtime - the end time, in milliseconds, class java DateTime.</p>
      <h2>notes</h2>
      <p> This table store notes of diary. Description of columns: _idn - record identifier(==_idt from &#34;times&#34; table); note - diary note for record</p>
      <h1>Export and import data base</h1>
      <p> In the settings, you can create your backup and recovery. Backup is saved in the memory card.</p>
      <p>Path: memory card/Android/data/maximsblog.blogspot.com.timestatistic/files</p>
      <p> When you import a file created with the name timestat, goes on a number as DD/MM/YYYY and expansion .db. This is a normal file sqlite, so for some editors need to change it to .sqlite.</p>
      <p> When you import dialog opens select the database. </p>
       ]]>
    </string>
</resources>